# CONTACTS

+996-551-130-187

✓ zumanovaliser814@gmail.com

@minimentor

Bishkek

in Jumanov Alisher

🚆 Jumanov07

# **LANGUAGES**

• Kyrgyz - native

• Russian - professional

• English - elementary

• Kazakh - professional

## **SKILLS**

HTML JavaScript

Scratch TypeScript

CSS React

SCSS Next

Bootstrap Redux Toolkit

Taiwind Router

Material UI RTK-Query

Figma Git/GitHub

Styled-Com.. Quick learner

Flexibility Teamwork

Leadership Communication

# **EDUCATION**

01.09.2023 - PRESENT

KSTU named after I. Razzakov

 Information security of automated systems

01.07.2022 - 31.03.2023

**Peaksoft House** 

• HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React

# **JUMANOV ALISHER**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm a Frontend developer with a passion for JavaScript, TypeScript, Next.js and React. With over a year of professional experience, I have specialised in building responsive and reusable UI components. My approach to development is based on the principles of Agile philosophy, I apply Scrum methodology, complementing it with Agile principles to organise a more predictable development process. In addition to technical skills, I also have an aptitude for teaching and mentoring. During this time, I have mentored more than 50 students. My passion for quality work and helping others succeed makes me a valuable team member.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Peaksoft House**

01.04.2023 - PRESENT

Frontend mentor

- Teaching students at all levels of proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React from beginners to experienced is my responsibility.
- Developing students' programming skills through personalized feedback and support.
- Creating a positive and inclusive learning environment that fosters collaboration and creativity is a key aspect of my job.
- Collaborating with colleagues to develop and improve instructional materials is also part of my remit.

## Peaksoft House

01.01.2023 - 31.03.2023

Frontend developer intern

- Participated in the "Gadgetarium" project, collaborating with backend specialists, a designer, and a project manager.
- Conducted tri-weekly meetings to distribute tasks and address emerging issues for "Gadgetarium".
- Led the frontend team as needed, ensuring tasks were completed efficiently and effectively.
- Invested significant time and effort into "Gadgetarium", enjoying the work and contributing to its success.
- Recognized for my performance with an additional role in the "MedCheck" project by the project manager.
- Managed responsibilities across both "Gadgetarium" and "MedCheck" projects concurrently.
- Built strong, collaborative relationships with all team members, including the backend team.

## **CERTIFICATES**

- 1. Graduate of the programming course Peaksoft House.
- 2. Participation in hackathon "Let's GoDigital 2.0".
- 3. Participation in hackathon "Let's GoDigital 3.0".
- 4. JavaScript HackerRank
- 5. Print Speed Ratatype

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Peaksoft House**

01.05.2023 - PRESENT

This is a website where you can find information about the company, its mission, and values. Additionally, you can register for courses offered by the company.

Tool: Next <u>Deploy</u>

#### Gadgetarium

01.03.2023 - 31.03.2023

This is online store where users can buy gadgets.

Tool: React <u>Figma</u>

#### MedCheck

01.03.2023 - 31.03.2023

This is a website to provide information on the clinic's medical services and to facilitate the process of recording patients.

Tool: React <u>Figma</u>

We applied the Agile philosophy in our projects, including conducting Stand-up meetings, managing tasks through the ClickUp website, and collaborating with Java developers, PM and designers.

And many other projects you can see in **GitHub**